

45 N Orchard St, Madison, WI, 53715, United States of America □ (+1) 608-770-1154 | Shyecheol.jang@wisc.edu | Dhyecheol123 (GitHub) | Diphyecheol (LinkedIn)

Summary .

Interested in finding optimized solution using Cloud (MS Azure) and writing understandable codes. Passionate about new technolgies/languages/solutions. Experienced in backend/frontend development, deployment/operation, and project management. Open to internship opportunities as a software developer or solution architect. Expect to graduate in Dec, 2023.

### Education

#### **University of Wisconsin-Madison**

Madison, WI, United States

Jul. 2018 - Current

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE; DOUBLE MAJOR IN STATISTICS; MINOR IN ENTREPRENEURSHIP

- Dean's List: Fa18, Sp19, Sp20 | GPA: 3.89/4.00
- · Library Technology Student Assistant at College Library, Memorial Library, and CALS Computing Lab

# Work Experience

#### **Korean American Scientist Association - Wisconsin Chapter**

Madison, WI, United States

DIRECTOR OF TECHNOLOGY (VOLUNTEER)

Dec. 2018 - Current

- Developed/Maintained NPO Chapter website and other useful IT tools for chapter management; responsible for various marketing, network activities, leadership board, and decision making.
- · Project Manager & Back-End Developer for KSEA-Wisconsin Event Ticket System Project (Aug. 2022 Current)
  - Building automated event ticket generation / admission service | Est. Release: Nov. 2022
  - Send QR code with ticket information to the customers, check ticket validity and todos during admission with officers' mobile device
  - Using Azure Function, Azure Blob Storage (for static website hosting), Azure Cosmos DB, CloudFlare (CDN) to minimize bandwidth, React Native
- Project Manager & Developer for KSEA-Wisconsin Website Rebuilding Project (Sep. 2019 Nov. 2019)
  - Built website for NPO Chapter | Led project, Collaborated with five developers | Used HTML, CSS, Jekyll, Git, Jira, MS Teams, Adobe XD
  - Divided tasks for collaboration accordingly | Provided training resources and counter errors and problems during the development process
  - Successfully minimized operation budget GitHub Pages to host; used CloudFlare (CDN) to minimize bandwidth
  - V2 project now launched (Est. Release: Dec. 2022) Add admin portal, elegant design, Next.JS-powered website; Serve on MS Azure

uniQon

TECHNICAL LEAD

Seoul, South Korea

Apr. 2020 - Oct. 2020

- Used NodeJS (TypeScript) and MongoDB to develop and operate API server, web page, and admin portal
- Elaborated idea and developed products that provide "real" college application data and mentor information to prospective applicants with their high school information, keywords from extracurricular activities, and target school lists and majors
- Closely collaborated with CEO to build concrete business plans | Trained Interns/Software Developers and engage in HR tasks
- · Implemented IT infrastructure and remote working environment with Microsoft Teams, Jira, and GitHub
- · Adopt Agile development workflow (Scrum) with weekly feedback to team/individuals | Traveled frequently for business meetings and recruiting

#### **Republic of Korea Army**

Busan, South Korea

Oct. 2020 - Jul. 2022

· Served at Wonkwang Nursing Home (Long-Term Care Facilities) to complete mendatory military duty of South Korea

# Projects\_

#### **BusanDevelopers Event Calendar**

SOCIAL SERVICE AGENT (SOCIAL WELFARE)

Busan, South Korea

Aug. 2021 - Jan. 2022

PROJECT MANAGER & FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

- Successfully built web event calendar for devleopers community | Led project, Collaborated with one back-end developer and one front-end developer
- Used React (MUI), NodeJS, Azure Cosmos DB, ExpressJS, and ReDoc | Manually set TypeScript React environment using ESLint, WebPack, and Babel
- Effectively divided the project into smaller milestones, manage teammates' performance, and conduct weekly meetings
- Back-End: github.com/BusanDevelopers/BGM-Event-Calendar-API | Front-End: github.com/BusanDevelopers/BGM-Event-Calendar-Webpage

#### **CloudFlare Public Dynamic IP Update Script**

Madison, WI, United States

DEVELOPER

Aug. 2019

- Built a script to update server's dynamic ip address to CloudFlare (DDNS) | Used Bash Shell Script | 50+ GitHub Star
- Source Code: github.com/hyecheol123/Cloudflare-Public-Dynamic-IP-Update

#### Honors & Awards

## AI-Blockchain Idea Pitching Competition (Third Edition)

Busan, South Korea

3RD PLACE AWARD

Aug. 2022

Presentation: Bird Strike Prevention Methods at Gadeokdo New Airport Using Big Data and Machine Learning

#### Skills

**Programming Language**: TypeScript, JavaScript, Java, SQL, R, C, Python, Bash

Cloud Service: Microsoft Azure AZ-900, AI-900, DP-900 Certified, Naver Cloud Platform, AWS, DigitalOcean (and VPS providers)

**DB**: Azure SQL, Azure Cosmos DB, mariaDB, mongoDB, redis

Misc: Linux/UNIX Server (Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS), Git, CloudFlare, React Redux, MUI (React Library), HTML, CSS, Arduino, Raspberry Pi

Language: English (Advanced), Korean (Native)